numis1.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU:**  
By registering with Numis Network (“Us”, “We”) you will receive an opt-in email to complete your registration. You must opt-in to be eligible for the FREE SILVER GIVEAWAY. You understand and agree that the information you submit allows us to make the Website, Promotions and Prizes available to you. You will only receive email from our company and representatives of our company. Accordingly, the information that you submit to us remains your property, but by registering with us, you grant us the right to use your name and likeness in our promotional materials. Any physical address information that is provided by winners of the Giveaway in order to ship prizes will not be shared with the public. 

**SECURITY:**  
We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users' Personal Information. When users submit Personal Information at the Website, their Personal Information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain any Personal Information offline). The privacy of your Personal Information is very important to us. We do not sell your contact information to any third parties or unrelated mailing lists. Access to your Personal Information is strictly limited, and we take reasonable measures to ensure that your Personal Information is not accessible to the public. The servers that we store Personal Information in are kept in a secure physical environment. 

**ELIGIBILITY:**  
Contest is open to residents of the United States, Canada, United Kingdom and Australia only. Entrants from outside these countries will not be considered for winning. 

**MINORS:**  
Individuals under the age of eighteen (18) are not permitted to register for or participate in any of the Promotions that we offer. No information should be submitted to, or posted at the Website by individuals under the age of eighteen (18) without the prior consent of their parent or guardian. Notwithstanding the foregoing, children thirteen (13) years of age and younger are not permitted to access the Website and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from such children. 

**REMOVAL OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION/OPTING OUT:**  
You can opt-out of receiving emails from our agency at the bottom of the first and subsequent emails you receive. However, deleting your Personal Information or otherwise opting-out of receipt of communications from us disqualifies you from future contest drawings. 

If you have any questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

FREESILVERNOW.com   
615 Channelsdie Drive   
Suite 201   
Tampa, FL.   
33602   
USA.   
Toll free: +1 (866) 920-1080  
Phone: +1 (813) 805-8706
